storecrowd.com 2016-01-19

# StoreCrowd - How we Protect your Privacy

## At StoreCrowd we value your Privacy!

This Privacy Policy is fairly simple; it's designed to make sure that your information is safe. Not only that we want to make sure that you have complete control over what happens with any information that you supply to StoreCrowd.

Entering any Personal information into the StoreCrowd site is completely optional. We do not require this from you to actually use our core functionality.

The following functionality on StoreCrowd will require personal information:

  1. Registering for an account
  2. Following a Store

We may use the email address provided by you to contact you from time to time, provided you have granted us permission to do so in your User Account.

If you register for an account there will be certain bits of information that other users of StoreCrowd will be able to view. This includes but is not limited to:

  1. Which Stores you follow
  2. Coupons you've added
  3. Reviews you've added

If you'd prefer for this information to not be made available, you can do so in your User Account.

StoreCrowd uses Session Cookies to identify returning & logged in users. We do not use this information in any other way.

Due to the nature of our site we link to many Third Party websites, these sites may require you to provide user information to them directly. Please ensure that you review the Privacy Policy & Terms on these sites to find out how they use your Personal Information.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

The StoreCrowd Privacy Policy may change from time to time as we add more products & services. As such we will alert existing users to the Privacy Policy change next time they log in, you may have to accept changes to continue using the site.

## Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

Created on 24th May 2009

## StoreCrowd Contact Information:

Crowd9 PTY LTD  
PO BOX 6565  
Melbourne  
VIC 3004 

Use our Contact Form to contact us.
